Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Men's and Women's Sports Files, 18.6 cubic ft.
  - Football, 6.18 cubic ft.
    - Ithaca Bombers, 1975 September 20 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Brockport Golden Eagles, 1975 September 27 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Southern Connecticut, Owls, 1975 October 18 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - RIT Tigers, 1975 October 4 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Norwich Cadets, 1975 October 25 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Albright Lions, 1975 November 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Plattsburgh Cardinals, 1975 November 8 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Springfield Chiefs, 1975 November 15 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Football, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Southern Connecticut, 1976 September 11 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Ithaca, 1976 September 18 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Brockport, 1976 September 25 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - RIT, 1976 October 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Cortland, 1976 October 16 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Norwich, 1976 October 23 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Football, 1976 October 30 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Plattsburgh, 1976 November 6 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Springfield, 1976 November 13 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Football, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Albany State Football Roster, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Football, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Football Reunion, 1977; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Football Season, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Football, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Football Season, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Albany vs. Buffalo, 1981 October 5 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Football, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Football Offense, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Football, 1982; 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Football, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Great Dane Football Program, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Football, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Football Recruitment, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Football Squad, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Football, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Football Banquets, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Football Rosters and Game Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Football Rosters and Game Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Football, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Football, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - The Great Danes Football Banquets, 1986-1990; 1992 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Football, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Football Statistics, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Football, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Football Squad, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Albany Football and Opponent Questionnaires, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Albany Football and Opponent Questionnaires, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - The Great Danes Football Banquet, 1989 November 19 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Football, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Football Statistics, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - JV Football, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Roster, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Great Dane Football Media Folder, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Football, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Great Dane Sports Publication, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Albany Football Records through 1990, ca.1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Football Clippings, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Albany Football Informative Folder, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Football, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Football Awards and Stats, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Football Banquet Programs, 1991-1995; 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Ithaca Football, 1992 September 12 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Springfield, 1992 September 18 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Brockport, 1992 September 26 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Alfred Saxons, 1992 October 13 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Union Football, 1992 October 10 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Cortland Football, 1992 October 17 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Norwich University, 1992 October 24 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Salisbury St, 1992 October 31 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Western Connecticut, 1992 November 7 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - St. Lawrence Football, 1992 November 14 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Football, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Football Statistics Working Chart and Notes, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Post Game Stats, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Football Season, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Football, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Ithaca College, 1993 September 11 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - St. Lawrence vs. University at Albany, 1993 September 18 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Football vs. Brockport, 1993 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Football at Alfred, 1993 October 2 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Football at Union, 1993 October 9 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Football at Cortland, 1993 October 16 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Albany vs. Norwich Football Homecoming, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Salisbury St, 1993 October 30 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Albany vs. Western Connecticut, 1993 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Football vs. William Paterson, 1993 November 13 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Football Banquet Programs, 1993 December 5 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Football, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Football Press Releases, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Football Scoring Summaries and Game Notes, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Football Season, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Football, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Football Scoring Summary, Ualbany vs. University of Dayton, 1995 September 2 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Season, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Football, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Football Team, 1996; 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Football Banquet Program, 1996 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Football Scoring Summaries and Game Notes, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Junior Varsity Football, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - 1996 Football Season, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Football Season, 1996-1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Football Season, 1996; 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Football Scoring Summaries and Game Notes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Giants VIP, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 1998 Football Season, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Football Game Notes, Albany vs. American International, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Football Season, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Hall of Fame, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Football, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 1999 Football Season, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Football, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - NCAA Albany Defensive Statistics Sheet, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Football, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Football Season, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Albany Great Danes Football Season Program, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Don Hansen's National Weekly Football Gazette Awards, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Football Season, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Football Scoring Summaries/ Game Program, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Football Season, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Squad, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Football, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Football Scoring Summaries / Game Programs, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Squad, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hofstra Football, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - New York Giants- New York Jets Combined Practice Program, 2005 August 6 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Football, CCSU, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Football, Fordham, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Hofstra Football, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Football, Maine, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Football Pre-Season, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Football, Sacred Heart, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Football, San Francisco University, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Football, Stony Brook, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Football, Summer, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Football, UMass (1 of 2), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Football, UMass (2 of 2), 2005 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Football Wagner, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Football, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Football Delaware, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Football Squad, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Football Records, Updated, 2006 August 2 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Football, Albany vs. Delaware Article, 2006 November 16 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Cornell Football, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Football, CCSU, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Football Fordham, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Football, Sacred Heart, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Football Scoring Summaries and Statistics, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Football, St. Francis, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Football Team and NEC, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Monmouth Football, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Robert Morris Football, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Stony Brook Football, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Wagner College Football, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Football Scoring Summaries, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Football Team Banquet, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Squad, 2007 September 10 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Samson Brown, Football, Interview Tips, 2008 June 12 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Football Banquet Program, 2008 November 23 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Football, Albany vs. Jacksonville Gridiron Classic, 2008 December 6 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Football, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Squad, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Football Scorebook, 2008, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Football, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Football Banquet, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Football Team, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Football, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Football Banquet, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Football Banquet Program, 2011 January 22 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Football, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Football Budget and Performance Evaluation, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Albany vs Colgate, 2012 September 1 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Albany vs Youngstown, 2012 September 15 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Albany vs Maine, 2012 September 22 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Albany vs Monmouth, 2012 September 29 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Albany vs Bryant, 2012 October 6 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Albany vs St. Francis, 2012 October 13 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Albany vs Sacred Heart, 2012 October 27 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Albany vs Wagner, 2012 November 3 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Albany vs Duquesne, 2012 November 10 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Albany vs CCSU, 2012 November 17 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Folder for Sports Information Director, Football Information to Lizzie, 2012 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Bob Ford, NYSHSFCA Skip Paridon Award, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Football Season, 2012-2013 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - CAA Football Schedule, 2013 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - 2012 and 2013 Football Banquet Programs, 2013-2014 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - 2014 Season Football Banquet, 2015 April 19 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - UAlbany Football Magnet, 2015 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Albany State Football History, Letters to Prospective Coaches, Undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Football Recruiting Pamphlet, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Great Dane All- Time Marks, Undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Golf, 0.15 cubic ft.
    - Golf, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Golf, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Golf, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Golf, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - SUNYAC Golf, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Golf, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Golf, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Golf, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Golf, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Golf, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Golf, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Golf, 1978-1979 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Women's Golf, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Women's Golf Schedule, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Women's Golf, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Golf Records, ca. 2003 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - America East Golf Championship, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - National Golf Coaches Association, All American Scholar Recipients, 2008-2010 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Women's Golf Roster, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - National Collegiate Golf, Albany Team, ECAC Tournament, 1970-1978; Undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Lacrosse, 1.6 cubic ft.
    - Lacrosse, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Lacrosse, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Lacrosse, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Men's Lacrosse 1 of 2, 1969-2008; Undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Men's Lacrosse 2 of 2, 1969-2008; Undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Lacrosse, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Lacrosse, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Men's Lacrosse Championship Certificate with Note, 1972; Undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Lacrosse, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Lacrosse, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Lacrosse, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Lacrosse, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Lacrosse, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Lacrosse, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 1987; 2015; Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - 1990 Men's Lacrosse (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - 1991 Men's Lacrosse (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - 1992 Men's Lacrosse (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - 1996 Women's Lacrosse Recruitment, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Women's Lacrosse Records/ Statistics, 1993-1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Women's Lacrosse Information, 1993-2002 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Media Forms Elizabeth Strusinski, Women's Lacrosse, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Men's Lacrosse Results, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Women's Lacrosse Results, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 1995 Men's Lacrosse Recruitment, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - University at Albany Women's Summer Lacrosse Competition, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 1996 Men's Lacrosse, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Men's Lacrosse Recruitment, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Women's Lacrosse Season, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Men's Lacrosse Records Since 1993, 1997; 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Season Men's Lacrosse, 1998; 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - 1998 Season Women's Lacrosse, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - 1999 Men's Lacrosse, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Men's Lacrosse Records Since 1992, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - 2002 Men's Lacrosse, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - 2000 Season Men's Lacrosse, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - 2001 Men's Lacrosse, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - 2001 Women's Lacrosse, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - America East Championship, Men's Lacrosse, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Men's and Women's Lacrosse Teams, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - 2005 Women's Lacrosse, 2004-2006 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Overall Men's Lacrosse Records, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Overall Women's Lacrosse Records, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2005-2009 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Syracuse vs. Albany, Men's Lacrosse, Official Game Program, 2006 April 21 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Lacrosse Men's, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Men's Lacrosse, Albany vs. Cornell, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Lacrosse Women's, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Rocky Bonitatibus, 2007; 2009; ca. 2010 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Men's Lacrosse and Women's Lacrosse, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Lacrosse, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Lacrosse Women's, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Daley Baker, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Jack Reynolds, 2009; ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Keith Olson, 2009; ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Travis Lyons, 2009; ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Anthony Ostrander, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Artie Marrapese, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ben Young, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Brendan Murphy, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Cody Futia, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Dean Steinmann, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Doug Eich, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Dwayne Stewart, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Edmund Cathers, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Jack Huber, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Jack Nickla, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Jon Newhouse, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Kevin Glueckert, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Men's Lacrosse Information and Game Notes, 2010-2011; 2013 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Matt Carello, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Matt Mackenzie, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Mike Miller, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Mike Woods, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Ryan Feurstein, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Tom Nuckel, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Ty Thompson, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Will Fuller, ca. 2010 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Miles Thompson, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Men's Lacrosse, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Women's Lacrosse, 2011 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Women's Lacrosse and Tournament Information, 2011-2013 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Men's Lacrosse Player Questionnaires, 2012-2013 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Women's Lacrosse Questionnaires, 2017 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - UAlbany Men's Lacrosse Schedule, Undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Sailing, 0.18 cubic ft.
    - Sailing Club, 1967-1969 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Sailing Club, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Sailing Club, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Sailing Club, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Sailing Club, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Soccer, 0.77 cubic ft.
    - Soccer, 1954-1975 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Men's Soccer Rosters, Stats, and Information 1950-1999, 1962-1982; 1984-1993; 1996-1999; Undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Soccer, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Soccer, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Soccer, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Soccer, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - SUNYAC Soccer, 1970-1972 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Soccer, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Soccer, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Soccer, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Soccer, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Women's Soccer, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Men's Soccer, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Women's Soccer, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Men's Soccer, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Women's Soccer, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Men's Soccer Statistics, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Men's Soccer, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Men's Soccer NCAA Information, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Academic Soccer Program Profile, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Women's Socccer, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Mens Soccer Brochure, 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Men's Soccer, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Men's Soccer Brochure, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Men's Soccer, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - Women's Soccer, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Men's Soccer, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Women's Soccer Game Programs, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Women's Soccer Goalkeepers and Players, ca. 1997 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Men's Soccer, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Women's Soccer, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Men's Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Women's Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Men's Soccer, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Women's Soccer, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Men's Soccer, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Women's Soccer, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 2002 Season Men's Soccer, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Womens Soccer, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Men's Soccer Game Programs, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Women's Soccer Game Programs, 2004 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Men's Soccer, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Men's Soccer Records, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Women's Soccer Records, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Men's Soccer Athlete Information, 2005; 2007 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Men's Soccer Game, Ualbany vs. Binghamton, 2006 October 18 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Women's Soccer Box Score, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Women's Soccer, 2006-2007 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Men's and Women's Soccer Match Programs, 2006-2007; 2009 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Men's Soccer Game Programs, 2006; 2009 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Men's Soccer Opponent Team Information, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Men's Soccer Statistics and Records, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Men's Soccer, 2011-2013; 2015 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Albany vs. UConn, Men's Soccer, 2016 November 12 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Softball Scorebooks, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Softball Schedule, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Softball, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Softball, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Softball, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Softball, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Softball, Great Dane Weekly Sports Wrap Up, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Softball Player information, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Softball, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Softball, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Softball Information, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Softball Records/ Statistics, 1993-1998 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Softball Clippings, 1993; Undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Softball Results, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Softball, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - NECC Softball Report, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - 1997 Softball, 1996-1998 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 1998 Softball, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Softball Box Scores, 1999 May (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Softball, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - 2000 Season Softball, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Softball Scorebook, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Softball, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Softball Scorebooks, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Softball, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Softball, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Bama Bash ( Tuscaloosa, Ala.), 2004 February 13-2004 February 15 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Softball, 2005 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Softball, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Softball Records, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - NCCAA Division I Softball Championship, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Softball Scorebook, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Softball Scoresheet Directions, Undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Softball, 0.5 cubic ft.
  - Swimming, 0.25 cubic ft.
    - Swimming, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Swimming, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Swimming, 1967-1977 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Swimming, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Swimming, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Swimming, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - SUNYAC Swimming, 1970-1973 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Swimming, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Swimming includes history since 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Swimming, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Swimming and Diving, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)